

About Me

I am a fresh graduate focused on web development with experience in building frontend applications using Vue, React, Tailwind CSS, and Hono. I have skills in creating responsive and interactive interfaces and understanding modern design concepts to deliver optimal user experiences. Committed to continuous learning and growth in the web development field, I am ready to tackle new challenges and contribute to a dynamic team.

Skills

- VueJs
- React
- Nuxt
- Git
- Hono
- Flutter

Softskills

- Effective Communication
- problem solving
- Teamwork
- Adaptive

Languages

Indonesian: Native English: Intermediate

FATHUR RAHMAN N

Front End Developer

Phone

+62-85183-114-789

Email

il 🎤

fathurrahmann.oman@outlook.com

Address

Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

Work Experience

July 2022 - November 2022

Frontend Web Developer

Koral Retail, FIT, Telkom University

• Developing a point of sales website-based application with Laravel and AlpineJs

January 2023 - January 2024

Mobile Developer

Research Grant, Integrated Electronic Waste Management Based on ICT, FEB, Telkom University

- Designing user interface with Figma.
- Implementing UI design to mobile view with Flutter.
- Developing Backend with Supabase.

September 2023 - January 2024

Mobile Development Course Practical Assistant

D3 Information Systems Study Program, FIT, Telkom University

- Assisting students in understanding the concept of mobile application development.
- Providing technical support and troubleshooting during the lab.
- Ensuring students follow good and efficient coding practices.

March 2024 - August 2024

Fullstack Web Developer

CoE Smarttourism and Hospitality, Telkom University

- Design and develop end-to-end web applications, from frontend to backend.
- Build interactive and responsive user interfaces using Vue and Tailwind CSS technologies.
- Implement APIs and backend logic using Hono.
- Debug, test, and deploy applications to production environments.

Educations

Information Systems Vocational

2021 - 2024

Telkom University

The Information Systems Vocational program provides practical skills in the field of information technology, including UI/UX, web development, data analysis, and mobile development, which prepares graduates for industry needs.

Certificate

Typescript Bootcamp: Beginner To Advanced (2024 Edition)

Angular University, Udemy